ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Administration Program Files. (Box 101)
  - Job Readiness Project-1st Ward 00W162 State Senator Bill Stachowski 3/8/01 Lipsitz, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 57)
  - Labor History for Youth 00W161 Coalition of Black Trade Unionists 2/24/01 Suggs, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 58)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships 00W160 A-E American Axle 4/4 - 4/12/2001 Henderson (Box 101, Folder 59)
  - Grievance Handling 00W159 Town of Cheektowaga Emp. Assoc. 3/31/2001 Lipsitz (Box 101, Folder 60)
  - Labor History 00W158 NYSUT (Southern Tier) 3/31/2001 Blair, 2000-2001 (Box 101, Folder 61)
  - Understanding Hiring / Evaluating Term.00W157 Modern Disposal, Inc. 4/28/01 Henderson, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 62)
  - Labor History 00W156 Bricklayers Local #45 3/2/2001 Lipsitz (Box 101, Folder 63)
  - PEL 00W155 UAW-GM 3/26- 3/29/2001 Wheaton (Box 101, Folder 64)
- Program Files-ILS Credit. (Box 102)
  - 93I028 UAW Region 9 93I028 "What's Afta NAFTA?" April 26-28. 1994 Blair (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Program # 93I021 Ford College Graduate/New Tech Hire Auto Industry Dynamics, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W021 Regional PEL: Auto Ind. In Transition 7/11 - 7/15/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W022 The Auto Industry in Transition 10/17 - 10/20/94 Blair/et al., 1994 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W02 The Auto Industry in Transition 11/14 - 11/17/94 Blair/et al., 1994 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W024 The Auto Industry in Transition 12/12 - 12/15/94 Blair/ et al., 1994 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W025 The Auto Industry in Transition 1/23 - 1/26/95 Blair/ et al, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W2026 The Auto Industry in Transition 2/13 - 2/16/95 Blair/ et al., 1995 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W027 The Auto Industry in Transition 3/13 - 3/16/95 Blair/ et al., 1995 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W028 The Auto Industry in Transition 4/24 - 4/27/95 Blair/et al., 1995 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W029 The Auto Industry in Transition 5/15 - 5/18/95 Blair/et al., 1995 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - UAW-GM-HRC 94W030 The Auto Industry in Transition 6/12 - 6/15/95 Blair et al., 1995 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W049 Focus on The People September 28, 1994 Henderson/Murak (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - IIS UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W053 Employment Maintenance 10/3 - 10/7/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W050 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 8/8/94 - 8/12/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W052 Employment Maintenance 9/19/94 - 9/23/94 Blair (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W05/94I/002 Employment Maintenance (230-052) 8/22 - 8/26/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W054 Employment Maintenance 10/17 - 10/21/94 Blair Cancelled, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - IIS-UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W055 Employment Maintenance 11/7 - 11/11/94 Blair, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC (Anaheim) 94W048 Many Face... Looking Forward 01/24/95 LJF, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC (Anaheim) 94W204 Script Development January 24, 1995 (94W048 + 94W205), 1994 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC (Anaheim) 94W205 Research and Design January 24, 1995 (94W048 + 94W204), 1994-1995 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC 94W206 Travel Costs Pre Acceptance of Proposal, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC 95W001 Employment Maintenance 7/31 - 8/3/95 Blair, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC 95W002 Employment Maintenance 8/14 - 8/17/95 Blair, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - UAW-Ford NEDTC 95W003 Employment Maintenance 9/11 - 9/14/95 Blair, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - Ford Motor Company 95W005 Ford College Graduate/New Tech Hires 04/24/96 Blair, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - Ford Motor Company 95W004 Ford College Graduate/ New Tech Hires 01/31/96 Blair, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - UAW FORD NEDTC 95W145 LIMA, OHIO AIS Geographic Pilot Program March 18 -21 1996 Fleron/Blair (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - UAW FORD NEDTC 95W146 Dearborn, MI AIS Geographic Pilot 3/25 - 3/28/96 Fleron/Blair, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - UAW FORD NEDTC 95W147 YOUNGSTOWN, AIS Geographic Pilot 4/15 - 4/18/96 Fleron/ Rubenstein, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - UAW FORD NEDTC 95W148 KANSAS CITY, MO AIS Geographic Pilot April 29 - 5/2/96 Fleron/Blair, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - Docs. Related to Travel for Cornell Univ. (Travel Vouchers), 1996 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - Holiday Inn, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 34)
- Management Programs. (Box 103)
  - UAW/Center for Human Resources Auto Industry in Transition 96W086 Auto Industry in Transition 96W086 3/10 - 3/13/97 Blair, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - UAW/GM Center for Human Resources Auto Industry in Transition 96W085 2/10 - 2/13/97 Blair, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - UAW/GM Center for Human Resources Auto Industry in Transition 96W084 1/13/97 - 1/16/97 Blair, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Auto Alliance International 96W082-9=83 The Value + Stenghth of People November 7, 21, 1996 Murak, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - IRRA 96W081 Hospital Mergers + The Implications January 22, 1997 Campagna (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - New Era Cap Independent Union 96W080 Legal Rights o Union Stewards March 1, 1997 Steinwald, D. (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Rosina Food Products, Inc. 96W079 Preventing Sexual Harassment 2/10/97 Campagna/Henderson Cane., 1997 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity 96W078 Americans with Disabilities Act April 30, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - University at Buffalo 96W077 Diversity Workshop 3/17 + 3/18/97 Murak/Henderson, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - SHRM, ERA, ASTD 96W076 Making Differences Work 3/19/97 Murak/Henderson (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - UAW Local 686 Retirees 96W075 Union Values at Work in the Community 2/4/79 Fleron, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W074 2001: A Vision in Progress February 7, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W073 2001: A Vision in Progress February 6, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W072 2001: A Vision in Progress February 5, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W071 2001: A Vision in Progress February 4, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W070 2001: A Vision in Progress February 3, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W063 2001: A Vision in Progress January 23, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W064 2001: A Vision in Progress January 24, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W065 2001: A Vision in Progress January 27, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W066 2001: A Vision in Progress January 28, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W067 2001: A Vision in Progress January 29, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W068 2001: A Vision in Progress January 30, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W069 2001: A Vision in Progress January 31, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W062 2001: A Vision in Progress January 22, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W061 2001: A Vision in Progress January 21, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - Outokumpu American Bras s96W060 2001: A Vision in Progress January 20, 1997, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W059 2001: A Vision in Progress January 17, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W058 2001: A Vision in Progress January 16, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W057 2001: A Vision in Progress January 15, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 95W056 2001: A Vision in Progress January 14, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 30)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W055 2001: A Vision in Progress January 13, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 31)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W054 2001: A Vision in Progress January 10, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 32)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W053 2001: A Vision in Progress January 9, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 33)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act 96W049 A Federal + NYS Analysis March 14, 1997 Campagna, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 34)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W050 2001: A Vision in Progress January 6, 1997 1st Shift, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 35)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W051 2001: A Vision in Progress January 7, 1997 1st Shift, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 36)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W052 2001: A Vision in Progress January 8, 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 37)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment 96W046 Part II Legal Issues for EEO/HR Mgrs. November 25, 1996 Campagna (Box 103, Folder 38)
  - Alternative Dispute Resolution 96W048 for Labor Relations Practitioners February 27, 1997 Woods/Lawson, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 39)
  - Privatization, Subcontracting 96W047 + Outsourcing: How to Fight + Win 12/7/96 Domaratz, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 40)
  - Auto Alliance International 96W042-45 The Value + Strength of People October 3, 10, 17, 24, 1996 Murak (Box 103, Folder 41)
  - NYS AFL-CIO 96W041 Organizing to Win 9/24 - 9/25/96 Blair, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 42)
  - ITT Fluid Technology Canc. 96W040 Customer Service Rep Training February 13 - 15, 1997 Woods, Lampen, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 43)
  - ITT Fluid Technology Canc. 96W039 Customer Service Rep Training February 6 - 8, 1997 Woods/Lampen, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 44)
  - NYS EAP 96W038 Skills + Strategy to Keep the Committee October 3, 1996 Woods, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 45)
  - NYS AFL-CIO 96W037 Labor and the Media September 9, 1996 Blair (Box 103, Folder 46)
  - Auto Alliance International 96W033-36 The Value and Strength of People 9/5/96 - 9/26/96 Murak, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 47)
  - NYNEX 96W032 Diversity in the Workplace October 11, 1996 Henderson (Box 103, Folder 48)
  - Veteran's Administration 96W031 High Performance Work Teams June, 1997 Woods/Henderson Cancelled, 1996-1997 (Box 103, Folder 49)
  - Veteran's Administration 96W030 Group Dynamics + Conflict Resolution March, 1997 Woods/LaLonde Cancelled, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 50)
  - WNYEIC 96W029 Can We Talk October 2, 1996 Woods/Henderson (Box 103, Folder 51)
  - SEIU Local 721 96W028 Mutual Gains Negotiation September 9, 1996 Woods (Box 103, Folder 52)
  - UAW/GM Center for Human Resources 96W027 The Auto Industry in Transition (PEL) 12/9 - 12/12.96 Blair et al., 1996 (Box 103, Folder 53)
  - UAW/GM Center for Human Resources 96W026 The Auto Industry in Transition (PEL) 11/11/96 - 11/14/96 Blair et al. Cancelled, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 54)
  - UAW/GM Center for Human Resources 96W025 The Auto Industry in Transition (PEL) 10/21/96 - 10/24/96 Blair/et al., 1996 (Box 103, Folder 55)
  - UAW/GM Center for Human Resources 96W024 The Auto Industry in Transition (PEL) 9/16 - 9/19/96 Blair et al. (Box 103, Folder 56)
  - PERB / Cornell ILR 96W023 Advanced PERB Litigation Practices October 30, 1996 Flaherty/ PERB (Box 103, Folder 57)
  - PERB / Cornell ILR 96W022 Overview of the Taylor Law October 30, 1996 Flaherty/ et al (Box 103, Folder 58)
  - Invitations Add/delete, 1994-1996 (Box 103, Folder 59)
  - Invitations DB, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 60)
  - Solution DB Add / delete, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 61)
  - Cast of Characters Additions, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 62)
  - 50th Invitation, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 63)
  - 50th Solicitation M/L, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 64)
  - 50th O/I/S, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 65)
  - Booklet Quotes, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 66)
  - 50th, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 67)
  - 50th Anniversary: 96W021 From Buffalo Roots: A Tribute October 7, 1996 Fleron/et al. (Box 103, Folder 68)
  - 50th Anniversary: Stories 96W020 + Sounds of an Era: Club Jazz September 8, 1996 Fleron/ et al. (Box 103, Folder 69)
  - Central Europe HR Education 96W019 Human Resource Issues July 30, 1996 Fleron, et al. (Box 103, Folder 70)
  - Buffalo State Residence Life 96W018 Diversity Henderson, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 71)
  - Outokumpu American Brass 96W017 Diversity Workshop August 23, 1996 Henderson (Box 103, Folder 72)
  - CSEA Seminar 96W016 October 16, 1996 Henderson (Box 103, Folder 73)
  - U.S. Immigration Service 96W015 Sexual Harassment September 17, 1996 Henderson/Equity (Box 103, Folder 74)
  - Auto Alliance, International 96W011-014 The Value + Strength of People August 1, 8, 22, 29, 1996 Murak (Box 103, Folder 75)
- Program manuals. (Box 104)
  - Writing the Collective Bargaining Agreement (2001) (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Writing an Affirmative Action Plan (1997) (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - World Auto Industry Toady Trans + Masters, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - World After 1989 (1990) (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Working Effectively in a Legal and Diverse Environment (1999) (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Workers, Unions and the Auto Industry (1990?) (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Workers, Unions and the Auto Industry (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Worker Adjustment to the Global Economy (1996) Part 2 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Workers, Unions, and the Auto Industry (1990) 5/7-5/11 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Worker Adjustment to the Global Economy (1996) part 1 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Work in America Institute (2001) OAB+UAWA Local 593 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Who's Who (2006) (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Who's Who (2005) (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - What's Afta NAFTA? (1994) Part 2, 1993-1994 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - What's Afta NAFTA? (1994) Part 1 Ver 2 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - What's Afta NAFTA. (1994) Part 2 Ver 1 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - What's Afta NAFTA (1994) part 1 Ver 1 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - USWA Staff Training Program, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Unions and the High Performance Workplace (1993) Ver 2 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Unions and the High Performance Workplace (1993) (Box 104, Folder 20)
- Administration-inactive File:Adjunct Faculty Personal data forms, independent contractors. (Box 105)
  - Syracuse, Michael Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1976-1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Sull, Errol Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1984-1985 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Stowell, David Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Stafford, Alan Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Solis, Yolanda Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Vitrano, Lisa A. Personnel - Actor's Equity, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Vulaj, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2001 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Wagner, Guy, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Walsh, Christopher Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Walsh, Mary Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (I/C or Firms), 1999-2000 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Warthog, Mary Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1988 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Watkins, Jeannette Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Watts, Bridget Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Way, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Wegman, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Smith Charles Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990-1997 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Smith, Frederic Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Joseph Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1980-1985 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Vena, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Vanwey, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Trumpfheller, Gladys Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-1980 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Truelsen, Jeff Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Truell, George Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Tirrell, Stanley Personnel- Adjunct Instructors, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Thomas Scott, Mary Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - Talty, Peter Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - A-F Personnel - Adjunct Instructors Resume Pool (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-2002 (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - A-F Personnel - Adjunct Instructors Resume Pool (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-2000 (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - List of Resumes (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Youngs, Paula Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 30)
  - White, Timothy - Deceased - Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 31)
  - Whalen, Jr., Richard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 32)
  - Welsh, Sandra Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 33)
  - Welborn, Steven K. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997-1998 (Box 105, Folder 34)
  - Q-V Personnel - Adjunct Instructors Resume Pool, 1990-2003 (Box 105, Folder 35)
  - L-P Personnel - Adjunct Instructors Resume Pool, 1990-1998 (Box 105, Folder 36)
  - G-K Personnel - Adjunct Instructors Resume Pool, 1993-2001 (Box 105, Folder 37)
  - Bios, 1965-1979 (Box 105, Folder 38)
  - Bad Guys, 1992-1994 (Box 105, Folder 39)
  - IIS Bios (Box 105, Folder 40)
  - Memorandum - Course Approval, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 41)
  - V-Z Personnel - Adjunct Instructors Resume Pool, 1991-1995 (Box 105, Folder 42)
  - Brumelfy, Charlene K., 1999 (Box 105, Folder 43)
  - Briggs, Vernon M. Jr., 1998 (Box 105, Folder 44)
  - Bock, Kristin Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 45)
  - Bishop, Ellen Grant Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 46)
  - Berkhoudt, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1989-2000 (Box 105, Folder 47)
  - Biondi, Angelo Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 48)
  - Bickert, Ronald Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 49)
  - Bianconi, Mark Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 50)
  - Bergevin, Brian Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 51)
  - Belliotti, Eileen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 52)
  - Beck, Joseph Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990-1991 (Box 105, Folder 53)
  - Bavaro-Phelan, Jacquelyn Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 54)
  - Barrington, Brian Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 55)
  - Bania, Joseph W. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 56)
  - Bakowski, Mary Ellen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 57)
  - Bahati Kuumba, Monica Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 58)
  - Baer, William L. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1993-1995 (Box 105, Folder 59)
  - Aurelio, Thomas G. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 60)
  - Aponte, Ingrid Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 61)
  - Andrews, Margaret Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 62)
  - Allen, Timothy Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 63)
- Administration-Active File:Adjunct Faculty Personal Data Forms, independent contractors. (Box 106)
  - Employee Earnings Record - Instructors 7/1/89 - 6/30/90 7/1/87 - 6/30/88hhh, 1987-1990 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Ahearn, Ellen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988-2005 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Robert N. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Balfour, Scott, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Banks, Jr., Proves Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990-2001 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Bantle, Douglas Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1989 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Bard, Geraldine Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Black-Hawkins, Melissa Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997-2000 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Bieger, Wayne Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Boyle, Rebecca T. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Brady, Patricia Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994-2005 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Bruce, Carole Personnel - Adjunct Instructor, 1981-2003 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Bruno, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (I/C or Firms), 2001-2005 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Campbell, Errol, 2002 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Cannon, Sr., Charles Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Daniel, Nicole, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Susan Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1986-1999 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Deely, Michael Personnel - Adjunct Faculty, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Delprino, Robert P. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1998-2002 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Creighton, Catherine A., 1999-2006 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Cook, Roger Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Cook, Roger Personnel - Adjunct Faculty, 1990-2006 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Cole, Paul Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981-2001 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Cohen, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Jeremy Cohen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 26)
  - Chodos, Linda Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000 (Box 106, Folder 27)
  - Chimera, Paul Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994-2003 (Box 106, Folder 28)
  - Casullo, Erin Personnel - Adjunct, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 29)
  - Bentivogli, Daniel Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988-2002 (Box 106, Folder 30)
  - Dimitrov, Danielle Personnel - Adjunct Instructor, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 31)
  - Deyo, Frederic Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988-2001 (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - Denisco, Kathleen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1985-1996 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - Flood, Lawrence Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-2001 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - Flaherty, Benard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - Finkel, Sidney Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992-2001 (Box 106, Folder 36)
  - Elsinghorst, Paula Personnel - Adjunct Instructor, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 37)
  - Elgie Levin, Donna Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992-1996 (Box 106, Folder 38)
  - Furlong PR, 2001-2002 (Box 106, Folder 39)
  - Furlong, Richard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988-1997 (Box 106, Folder 40)
  - Gallant, Ellen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 41)
  - Giroux, Jr., E. Joseph Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1985-2002 (Box 106, Folder 42)
  - Gettings, Carol E Personnel - Adjunct, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 43)
  - Lacher, Jeffrey Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 44)
  - Cullinan Szvoren, Helen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992-1996 (Box 106, Folder 45)
  - Curlee, Maurice Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2001-2005 (Box 106, Folder 46)
  - Disare, Melinda Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1996-1997 (Box 106, Folder 47)
  - Dolce, Frank Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1989 (Box 106, Folder 48)
  - Donovan, Kevin J. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 49)
  - Duncan, Jr., James Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 50)
  - Dziedzic, Thomas Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990-2001 (Box 106, Folder 51)
  - Eames, Dennis, 2005 (Box 106, Folder 52)
  - Thomas Frank + Fried, Emanuel Personnel, Adjunct Instructors, 1984-2005 (Box 106, Folder 53)
  - Fricano, Thomas, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 54)
  - Forsyth, Daniel P Personnel - Adjunct Faculty, 2002 (Box 106, Folder 55)
  - Freitag, Leonard, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 56)
  - Franey, Michael, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 57)
  - Fordham, Monroe Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 58)
  - Henry, M. Beth, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 59)
  - Haynes, Jr., Curtis Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994-2002 (Box 106, Folder 60)
  - Bonnie Hackford, 2004-2006 (Box 106, Folder 61)
  - Grippi, Jeanne Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981-2001 (Box 106, Folder 62)
  - Grande, William Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1989-2007 (Box 106, Folder 63)